rivermarkcu.org 2015-12-27

# FACTS

                                                                                                                Rev. 09/2014
               RIVERMARK COMMUNITY CREDIT UNION PRIVACY POLICY
                               WHAT DOES RIVERMARK COMMUNITY CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR
 FACTS                         PERSONAL INFORMATION?
 Why?                          Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law
                               gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us
                               to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this
                               notice carefully to understand Rivermark Community Credit Union’s Privacy Policy.
 What?                         The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the accounts or
                               services you have with us. This information can include:
                                     Name, address, Social Security number, and income
                                     Account balances and transaction history
                                     Credit history and credit scores
 How?                          All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their
                               everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can
                               share their members’ personal information; the reasons Rivermark Community Credit
                               Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                          Does Rivermark
                                                                                                     Can you limit this
 Reasons we can share your personal information                          Community Credit
                                                                                                         sharing?
                                                                           Union share?
 For our everyday business purposes—
 such as to process your transactions, maintain your
                                                                                Yes                         No
 account(s), respond to court orders and legal
 investigations, or report to credit bureaus
 For our marketing purposes—
                                                                                Yes                         No
 to offer our products and services to you
 For joint marketing with other financial companies                             Yes                         No
 For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                                Yes                         Yes
 information about your transactions and experiences
 For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                                 No                   We don’t share
 information about your creditworthiness
 For nonaffiliates to market to you                                              No                   We don’t share
                                     Call 800.452.8502 or 503.626.6600
                                     Visit us online: https://www.rivermarkcu.org/forms/privacy-opt-out
To limit
our sharing                   Please note: When you are no longer our member, we will not share your information
                              except as permitted or required by law or as described in this notice.
                              However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?                     Call 800.452.8502 or 503.626.6600; or go to www.rivermarkcu.org

What we do
How does Rivermark Community Credit       To protect your personal information from unauthorized
Union protect my personal information?    access and use, we use security measures that comply with
                                          federal law. These measures include computer safeguards
                                          and secured files and buildings. We also restrict access to
                                          nonpublic personal information about you to those employees
                                          and other persons who need to know the information to
                                          provide products or services to you.
How does Rivermark Community Credit       We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Union collect my personal information?        open an account or apply for a loan
                                              apply for any credit union service
                                              visit our website, provide us information on any online
                                               application or transaction, or information you send to us by
                                               email.
                                              use your credit or debit card or pay your bills
                                              make deposits to or withdrawals from your accounts
                                          We also collect your personal information from others, including
                                          credit bureaus or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?            Federal law only gives you the right to limit information sharing as
                                          follows:
                                              sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information
                                               about your creditworthiness
                                              affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                              sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                          State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights
                                          to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing for an  Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
account I hold jointly with someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates                                Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                          financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                              Our affiliate is Rivermark Insurance Agency.
Nonaffiliates                             Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can
                                          be financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                              Rivermark Community Credit Union does not share with
                                               nonaffiliates so they can market to you except for our joint
                                               marketing arrangements.
Joint marketing                           A formal agreement between Rivermark Community Credit Union
                                          and a nonaffiliated financial company where we jointly market
                                          financial products or services to you.
                                              Our joint marketing partners include financial service providers.
